indiacom.com 2019-04-21

# Privacy Policy - Indiacom.com

This website is owned and run by Indiacom Limited. In this privacy policy, we will refer to Indiacom Limited using the terms 'Indiacom', 'us', 'we' and 'our'. If you use our online services, or any of our other services to find businesses or any other information, we will call you a 'user' in this policy. 

This Policy sets out policies and practices adopted by Indiacom about how we collect, use and secure the information/listing of Businesses or individuals using this website. We may from time-to-time revise this privacy policy, and the date of last revision will be at the bottom of this page, so please be sure to check back periodically. By visiting the Website, you are acknowledging and accepting this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after changes have been posted to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes. 

With a view to meet the information needs of the users at large Indiacom offers the online website www.indiacom.com. Indiacom respects the privacy of its users and strives to protect it to the maximum extent possible. 

The policy explains 

A. The information we collect and how we do it 

1\. What information we collect? 

We collect, interalia, the following information about Business Organisatons, and Professionals –both in the public and private domain: 

(a) Name of individual/organization 

(b) Name of the Decision Maker/Contact person (in case of Organisation/Business) 

(c) Category of Business of the organisation/Profession of the Individual 

(d) Mailing Address(s) 

(e) Landline Telephone Number(s) and/or mobile phone number(s) 

(f) Email Id(s) 

(g) Latitude and Longitude indicating the physical location of the entity 

(h) Any other Information as may be required from time to time. 

Indiacom, in no way, collects Sensitive personal data or information of a person as illustrated under rule (3) of the Information Technology (Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011. We advise you not to provide such type of information to us or any person associated with us, under any circumstances. You hereby acknowledge that Indiacom shall not be held responsible for any damages or losses or claims occurred to you, arising out of providing us with such information. 

2\. How we collect Information?

We have employed human resources to collect information (Contents) published in the Website. We also collate information from authentic published sources and validate it independently. The information collected by Indiacom are either freely available or accessible in public domain or furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force or provided by the business entity or professional or organisation on its own accord for publication. The users of this site also provide a vital portion of the Contents of the Site 

3\. When and why we will contact you? 

On receipt of the information provided by you, we may contact you, periodically, for confirming the validity of the information provided by and with your permission we may also provide or offer you the information about products and services of Indiacom, for enhancing your business prospect and thus build business relation with you. We may record or monitor the calls we make to you, or you make to us. We do this for security and training purposes and to improve the services we provide. We may also ask you to send us your consent letter, duly signed by you through post or fax or email. In case you opt to send your consent letter through email, you shall affix your electronic signature to that email otherwise the said email will be considered solely at the discretion of Indiacom and treated as valid or invalid based upon enquiry/verification, and your request may or may not be considered.. We require your said consent for the purpose of publishing/using of such information as provided in this Privacy Policy. You have the right to withdraw such consent at any time by writing a letter, properly signed, addressing to the Grievance Officer of Indiacom (details mentioned at the end of this policy). 

B. Publication of Information 

The information provided by the Users will be published on Indiacom website after due verification and permission of the user as stated above, wherever considered necessary. You acknowledge that Indiacom may publish the information provided by you online i.e. its website and also on the print media like Yellow pages, directories etc. 

C. Purpose and Use of Information

Information provided/collected, including Personal information may be shared with other organizations or individuals – both private and public to whom Indiacom licenses its Contents, in connection with services that they perform under a lawful contract. Our agreements with organizations ensure that personal information can only be used for the purposes for which it was shared with them, and that they handle the personal information in accordance with this Statement. Some of our licensed organizations/companies are located/Head quartered abroad and as such, are subject to foreign laws, including laws that may require disclosure of personal information to government agencies in those countries. We may share your personally identifiable information with other companies including associate Companies of Indiacom, and will require the recipient to comply with the provisions of this privacy policy. As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company, if this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including personally identifiable information. However, personally identifiable information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. Indiacom may also share personal information with other third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our users etc. 

We also use third party service providers to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume, statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for advertisers. Please note that this is not personally identifiable information, only general summaries of the activities of our users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us. 

The said information may also be provided to authorised Government agencies for investigative, protective, cyber security activity, on receipt of a lawful order. 

Use of Links: The Website may contain links to third-party websites. This is done for the convenience of the user. Indiacom is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

D. Security – Data Protection 

The information/content (database) published on the Indiacom online site, are securely stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the said servers is password protected and is strictly permitted to only a few authorized staff of Indiacom Limited or any other authorized professional for the purpose to comply with their job functions. However, we cannot guarantee you the security of our database, nor we can guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the internet. You hereby acknowledge that not to hold Indiacom responsible from any failure in breach of such security and you release us from any and all claims arising out of use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner. 

E. Information of Professionals 

The Information/Listing details regarding advocates / attorneys / lawyers or any other professional bodies established/authorised under any regulatory body for such profession, are meant solely for the purpose of providing information and not for the purpose of advertising. The information regarding these professionals shall be used by you only for your personal purposes and not for any other uses. This listing details does not amount to any form of advertising or soliciting by those professionals listed and are in no way of violation of professional ethics framed for lawyers by the Indian Bar Council and or any other regulatory body of professional.“ 

F. Do-not-call (DND Condition) 

The listings published or hosted in this website may contain the telephone or mobile contact details of the concerned Business organisation(s) or individual(s). If you desire to contact those Business organisation(s) or individual(s) using that telephone or mobile number, then in that case you are required to check the DND (do-not-call registry) status using the following link http://www.nccptrai.gov.in/nccpregistry/search.misc, and follow the relevant TRAI regulations and any other applicable regulations as may be applicable. 

G. Google Analytics 

We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitors' behaviour on our website in order to learn about the kind of users that visit our site, and possibly target future advertising or tune our content based on that. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.

We also use other Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (e.g. Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick campaign Manager integration or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). Visitors can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customise Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings Indiacom will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick cookie unless you have robust notice of, and the user's prior affirmative (i.e. opt-in) consent to, that merger. Visitors to our website may also use the following Google tool to opt-out: Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on 

H. Grievance Officer 

If you have any queries relating to the above mentioned privacy policies; please send us an email at corporate@indiacom.com.

You can also reach us by mail or by telephone: Indiacom Limited, Hermes Heritage, Phase I (Commercial), Shastri Nagar, Pune – 411006, Maharashtra. Tel.: 020-26603800. 

In case, you want to update/remove the information provided by you or published in the website or you have any complaint regarding this website or any contents thereof, you may please contact our grievance officer in writing using the address or by email(with electronic signature) given below: 

To  
The Grievance Officer,  
Indiacom Limited Hermes Heritage,  
Phase I (Commercial),  
Shastri Nagar, Pune – 411006,   
Maharashtra, India   
Tel.: 020-26603854  
Email – corporate@indiacom.com

On receipt of the request, the Grievance Officer will take necessary steps, within a reasonable time, to ensure that the data shown on the website is updated/removed as requested or proper action is taken to redress your complaints. 

* * *

Note: This privacy policy is framed in compliance with the cyber laws rules notified time to time by "Department of Information Technology, Ministry of Communications and Information Technology, Govt. of India". 

Last Updated Date: 1st-February-2012
